Kunal Singh

Ph. no: +91 7978039899, +91 8763206647 Email: kunalrajput267@gmail.com

Summary of experience:

A dynamic professional with more than 3 years of experience as a Relationship Manager at leading banks.

Experience in handling daily banking operations along with building good relationship with the customers along with managing a small team to sell banking solutions and drive sales and revenue generation goals.

Educational Qualifications:

- ✓ Post Graduate Diploma in Banking from **Manipal University** in the year 2016
- ✓ Mutual Fund Distributors Certification by National Institute of Securities Markets (NISM) in 2016
- ✓ Depository Operations Certification by NISM in 2016
- ✓ Certification done in **GOLD AUDITOR COURSE**

Qualification	College/School	University/Board	Year	Aggregate %
B.Com (Hons)	Dharanidhar Autonomous College	North Orissa University	2015	61.38
12 th	D.D. JR College	CHSE	2012	65.33
10 th	St. Teresa's School	ICSE	2010	59.4

Work Experience:

Worked in **ICICI Bank** from October 2016 to January 2020 as Deputy Manager Worked in **IndusInd** Bank from February 2020 to July 2020 as Manager

Strengths and Skills:

- ✓ Passionate and responsible towards my work, social, disciplined and ready to take initiatives
- ✓ Flexible and Capable of working in a challenging environment
- \checkmark Good Knowledge of FINACLE software used for Banking operations
- **▼ Tools:** Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint **Operating System:** Windows 10

Work Details:

Company IndusInd BANK

Location Mumbai - Andheri West Branch

Duration Feb 2020 – July 2020

Designation Manager

Responsibilities

✓ Opening Trade accounts for Import Export Customers

✓ Providing proper solutions - connect online facility, Letter of credit, Bank Guarantee facility, Overdraft facility for customers uninterrupted business..

✓ Earn Revenue for Bank through third party products as well as handle daily banking operations and customer service.

Company ICICI BANK

Location Mumbai - Andheri West Branch

Duration Oct 2016 – Jan 2020
Designation Relationship Manager

Responsibilities

✓ Handle day to day banking operations and customer requests.

- ✓ Handling team of sales personnel for sales related targets and customer service.
- ✓ Assistance to existing customers in helping and resolving their issues.
- ✓ Encourage and help the customers in opening new accounts or availing suitable products and services.
- ✓ Setting up meetings with valuable clients for developing and maintaining good relations and also cater to their needs or issues.
- ✓ Initiate sales activities with the customers through cross selling.

Personal Information:

Father Name	K K Singh
Date Of Birth	07 May 1992
Gender	Male
Languages Known	English, Hindi, Oriya
Marital Status	Single
Address	Room no 307, B wing, Amarnath Apartments, Andheri East, Mumbai - 400069
Nationality	Indian

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all statements made in the application are true, complete and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Mumbai Kunal Singh